

My Contact

atifsalehin950@gmail.com

+8801744187326

229,Moghbazar-Noyatola, Dhaka-1217

Skills

- Social Media Managing
- Voiceover Artist
- Ad Video Editor
- Graphic Design
- Data Entry & processing
- Social Media Marketing
- Copywriting
- Article Writing
- Sales/Idea Management
- Basic Computer skills (MS word/PowerPoint/Excel)

Education Background

National Bank Public School

Secondary School Certificate Completed in 2018 G.P.A. 5.00

Government Science College

Higher Secondary School Certificate Completed 2020 G.P.A. 5.00

University of Asia Pacific

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science & Engineering From 2022 - Present G.P.A. so far 3.53

Achievements

2022 - **Winner of Quiz Competition** Software and Hardware Club

2023 - **1st Runner up of Idea Season 2.0**Entrepreneurship and Career
Development Club

Md. Atif Salehin

DIGITAL MARKETER

About Me

Having worked extensively in voice acting, video editing, and social media management, I take great satisfaction in producing excellent work on all platforms. I am well-known for my unwavering enthusiasm, dependability, and work ethic. I routinely surpass expectations and thrive in difficult circumstances. My versatility shows through in my ability to work both independently and as a team member.

Professional Experience

Dana n Decor

Junior Social media Designer / Social Media Manager

2019 - 2021

- Analyzing engagement data.
- Social media marketing.
- Product Idea designing.
- Identifying trends in customer interactions
- Planning digital campaigns

Echithi

Information Analysis and Data Entry Executive

2022 - Present

- Data entry.
- Input data and verifying accuracy.
- Creating data backups as part of a contingency plan.

Fiverr

Professional Voiceover Artist & video Ads Editor

2023 - Present

- Versatile Vocal Range
- Emotional Resonance
- Adaptability to Scripts
- · Professionalism and Reliability

Volunteer experience

- ICPC World Finals, Dhaka, 2022
- Brake The Barriers, Workshop 2023
- VOLUNTEER, Directorate of Students' Welfare

My Reference

Zaforullah Momtaz

Abrar Al Rawnak

Dana N Decor / CEO +46732441395

Echithi / General Manager +8801723722788